[Love Has Fireworks]
[Episode 6]
What do you mean?
I-Is the food poisoned?
No, no.
N-No, it's not poisoned.
It really isn't, I swear.
I swear it's not poisoned!
No, it's just that...
I want you to help me revise
my research report.
Can you help me?
A research report?
You almost scared me to death.
You finished it so quickly?
Yes, but it's not perfect yet.
I was thinking,
since you're one of the people in charge
of the Shanlifang IPO project,
it would be great if you could
give me some advice.
I see.
You want to use this
to win Fang Yun over.
Exactly.
That would be a huge favor.
It's so huge
that one meal isn't nearly enough.
Unless...
Unless what?
You want a rent reduction?
A hundred yuan is the max.
You think I'm a money-grubber
like you?
Unless you willingly call me your teacher.
What? You don't want to?
Have you heard the story
of the one-word teacher?
In ancient times,
just for changing one word,
people would become someone's student.
You are just too reluctant to learn.
No, that's not what I meant.
I mean,
I don't even know
if your advice is good or not yet.
Are you doubting me?
Fine. Very well.
It's a bit of a waste of my talents,
but I'll condescend
to check it out for you.
Bring me the research report.
Really? Just a moment!
Here, take a good look.
[Comprehensive Research Report
of the Shanlifang Hotel]
[Solidifying the Industrial Layout
While Awaiting the Right IPO Window]
[Comprehensive Research Report
of the Shanlifang Hotel]
[Solidifying the Industrial Layout
While Awaiting the Right IPO Window]
Wait, what's with that expression
of yours?
Your eyebrows are k-knitted together.
Is it that bad?
Really?
-Can you let me focus on analyzing it?
-Wait, you can just tell me...
Be quiet for a moment.
Let me analyze it properly.
Then take your time to take a good look.
Is it that bad?
♪ No need to guess the ending
right from the beginning ♪
♪ Let the melody play
among the chords and the wind ♪
♪ And no need to demand
that yesterday keeps its promises ♪
♪ Leave some surprises in life
to the unknown ♪
[Zhao De]
♪ Also, there's no need
to force the closest bonds ♪
Hello.
♪ I might be left alone,
but I have your warmth ♪
I've figured out a solution
for the Shanlifang matter.
Just lead the team to work normally.
I will handle the rest.
♪ And there's no need to dwell
on right or wrong—not because of fear ♪
Okay.
♪ A hug far outweighs endless apologies ♪
♪ I'll show you the wider world ♪
♪ It's only in blazing bright
that I am who I am ♪
♪ Quietly carry it all, like a harbor
sheltering your drifting soul ♪
How is it? Huh?
Not bad.
♪ When you return to your peaceful life ♪
I told you there definitely
isn't any problem with what I wrote.
♪ The light at home glows warm
day and night ♪
Not exactly.
There are many places
that need to be revised. Here.
Tell me about it.
♪ Stay forever by each other's side ♪
♪ Like the stars and the moon
hanging brightly in the sky ♪
Look.
♪ I'll show you the wider world ♪
Shanlifang Hotel Group
has a significant difference
in market positioning,
♪ It's only in blazing bright
that I am who I am ♪
so there is no such thing
as industrial competition.
♪ Quietly carry it all, like a harbor
sheltering your drifting soul ♪
That's awesome, teacher.
♪ When you return to your peaceful life ♪
You are seeing me as your teacher already?
That's so quick.
♪ The light at home glows warm
day and night ♪
When it comes to research reports,
I should really learn from you.
But you are still far
from officially being my teacher.
♪ Stay forever by each other's side ♪
This is how you repay people
after using them?
No, it's not like that.
♪ Like the stars and the moon
hanging brightly in the sky ♪
I'll cook for you. You pick the day.
That's more like it.
So this also needs to be revised, right?
Of course, it needs a revision.
I've been talking about it for a while.
Do you even remember it?
Aren't you going to sleep?
I won't hit the sack until I'm done.
Fine.
I've noticed that you're pretty efficient
in getting things done.
But I'm just wondering.
If you were like this before,
you wouldn't have worked until now
just to reach this position.
I was silly before.
For the so-called family
and resource allocation,
I wasted plenty of opportunities.
Come on.
Don't flatter yourself.
I've heard this kind of talk a lot.
Were you being held at gunpoint
and forced to make that decision or what?
People just use this as an excuse
to avoid competition
and settle for the status quo, you know?
You're actually
quite interesting sometimes.
What makes you say so?
When other girls broke up,
they cried and made a scene.
But you've been acting
as if nothing happened.
Did the feelings and love fade away
after such a long time,
or did you realize it was no big deal
after breaking up?
That's not right.
The longer you're together,
the deeper the feelings.
When love fades,
family affection and friendship
get mixed in.
Losing this kind of love
will cause you intolerable agony.
I really don't see that in you.
Do I have to wail
or make a scene to look sad?
Do you think I have time to be sad?
Is my research report done,
or have I found a job,
or do I no longer have a mortgage to pay?
That person was
the biggest bug in my life plan.
After the patch,
he doesn't need to exist anymore.
All done.
Thank you, Li Yifei.
You're up?
I'm heading out.
Have the meal on your own.
Where are you going?
I'm going on a date.
With whom?
Take a guess.
I won't.
Just guess.
Just tell me.
With Qian Fei and Dang Yu.
Who else could it be? Come on...
Qian Fei and Dang Yu?
I don't think so.
Are you going on a date
with your little lover?
Otherwise,
why is someone not wearing her ring?
You are measuring
the stature of a great man
with a petty man's mind.
I knew you would ask that.
Just think about it.
Fei went through a breakup not long ago.
Would it be appropriate for me
to wear a huge diamond ring
and show up in front of her?
[Poming, my level is low now
because I accidentally]
[gave my gear away.]
[You know what I've really got.]
[How about you take a look
at my recent stats?]
[Please give me a chance
to join the team. Please!]
[Big Brother Poming,
I got two new pieces of gear.]
[Poming, I'm grinding
to improve my stats.]
Son, no matter what,
you need to eat something.
I'm not eating!
Leave me alone.
[Please think about it
and give me another chance, will you?]
Come on, let me propose a toast.
We've gathered here today
to celebrate our bestie
moving into a new house
and dumping the jerk.
Right!
And she's starting a new chapter in life.
Cheers.
I'm starving.
Why are you in such a hurry?
How could I not be?
The meal was delayed
until now just to wait for you.
You must be starving.
Fine, have this piece of meat.
It's hot!
Have some more.
Yu, you have quite an appetite.
It's honestly a bit scary.
If you worked as much as I did,
you'd be the same as me.
Are you really planning
to go back to He Jing?
Yes.
I'm not doing it just for the money.
I also want to prove my capabilities.
I don't want to stay
in my comfort zone anymore.
Do you have to stick to this one path?
He Jing isn't the only choice
in the industry.
But He Jing is the industry benchmark.
Exactly.
Besides, I don't have
any front desk experience.
If I work with Director Fang,
I can avoid a lot of detours.
But if you join her project team,
you'll have to take charge
of the Shanlifang project.
What's wrong with that?
Are you afraid
that if I'm in the same project team
as that person, it will be awkward,
and people will gossip about us?
Yeah, didn't I tell you before?
If those people in the office
learn about it,
rumors will spread for sure.
It's fine.
You don't need to worry about it at all.
A clean hand wants no washing.
I have nothing to do with him.
It's not about
whether you're afraid or not.
You need to be cautious.
Anyway, just don't tell anyone about it.
Anyway, I won't let
any of them visit my house.
[Resume of the Newly-Appointed Staff
in Finance Department Management]
[Wang Ruohai, Finance Department]
[Resume of Wang Ruohai,
Finance Department]
[Shanlifang Group Personal Resume]
[Basic Information: Name—Wang Ruohai]
That's weird.
Doesn't my landlady know
that her ex-boyfriend
works at Shanlifang?
She probably doesn't know.
Otherwise, she wouldn't be so eager
to join Fang Yun's project team.
So what my landlady will face is
seeing her ex-boyfriend
and his current girlfriend every day.
[Awards: Outstanding Manager
of Nalan Maide Bank]
And they are the clients
she must obey.
Even I don't dare to think about it
any further.
Here you are, Fragrant Grass.
This is so beautiful.
Someone's been texting you.
Aren't you going to reply?
Take a look for me. It's my alt account.
So many messages.
[This is all a man-made disaster.
Please help me. I can't take it anymore.]
[As long as you give me a chance,
I can do anything.]
[Saving a life is more meritorious
than anything else, Poming.]
Take a look yourself.
This man just won't stop.
Ignore him. He's just a psycho.
You have an admirer?
What admirer?
It's the one I told you
who wanted to join the team,
Prime Minister.
Poming, Poming, bro.
[Big Brother Poming, GOAT, legend,
are you still there?]
He thinks you are a man?
That's exactly what I want.
I never disclose
my personal information online.
He's sent you so many messages.
If you're not even replying,
it'd be so pitiful.
You're always the soft-hearted one.
Fine, since you said so,
I'll text him back.
Cheers.
You're probably a minor, huh?
Focus on your studies
and don't fall behind.
I'm an adult, and I'm super reliable.
You can test me if you don't believe it.
I have no time for that.
Can I be a backup?
A backup?
Our team rarely has
any special situations.
The chance
for a backup to play is almost zero.
It doesn't matter!
I can be a backup and do chores
at the same time.
Do you have that much leisure time?
As long as I can contribute to the team,
I'm even willing to skip sleep.
You said it.
Don't complain
that I maltreat you in the future.
No, I won't!
Dear Poming,
just rest assured and leave this to me.
[Warmonger Soul: Prime Minister]
All right, we're leaving Jingjing to you.
Don't worry.
I promise I'll treat her well,
although
I'll never be able
to compete with her besties
for a chance to have dinner with her.
Alright, stop acting pitiful.
After I successfully join
the Shanlifang project team,
we will have a great meal again.
This time,
family members are allowed to join.
Shanlifang...
We two will come for it together.
We'll take our leave.
We will come together.
Alright, alright.
S-Stop being so lovey-dovey
in front of me.
Are you nuts?
Hurry up and leave.
We're leaving.
We'll be going then.
-Bye.
-Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
I should probably get going, too.
I'm leaving this wine for you.
How can I finish all this wine?
We can drink it next time we come.
Make sure you keep it well.
Got it.
Why are you here?
Couldn't I come over
to my bestie's place for a meal?
Oh, right, you are the bestie
of Yifei's landlady.
Are you here for Li Yifei?
You are not drunk this time, are you?
I promise I didn't drink.
Okay.
Remember to go back early.
Well...
My name is Jun Cheng.
May I have your name, please?
I'm Dang Yu.
Dang Yu.
I'm really sorry
about what happened last time.
It's fine.
I was just teasing you at the bar.
Don't feel bad.
I threw you down, too.
Let's just call it even.
Alright, then, let me treat you
to a meal some other time.
There's really no need.
I'm usually quite busy.
Don't get me wrong.
I mean...
Qian Fei is your bestie,
and Yifei is my good buddy.
If you think
it's awkward for us to have a meal alone,
I can ask the two of them to join us.
Man, you're quite sincere.
Okay, let me see when I have time.
I'll WeChat you.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
I'll wait for your message.
Wait, she didn't give me her WeChat.
So Qian Fei still doesn't know
that Wang Ruohai has joined Shanlifang?
No, she doesn't.
Then you should tell her.
Think about what she has to face—
a cheating ex-boyfriend
and his current girlfriend,
who is also the heiress of Shanlifang.
It's too messy.
What a mess.
So do you want her to join or not?
Do you think
she really wants to have dinner with me,
or she's just brushing me off?
I'm asking you something. Don't ignore me.
Neither.
Then what is it?
She couldn't even be bothered
to brush you off.
No way, you have to help me.
How?
At least help me
get her contact info, right?
Are you actually falling for her?
I really don't know
if I'm falling for her or not,
but I just feel that
she's different from others.
How is she different?
Think about it.
One second she's
such a petite and cute girl,
and the next, boom,
she suddenly threw you to the ground.
How impressive was that?
Are you a masochist or something?
I don't think so.
Anyway, I just feel
that she has many different sides.
I want to learn more about her.
I only know she is Qian Fei's colleague
and works at He Jing Securities.
Anything else?
That's all.
You'll have to dig out the rest yourself.
No way!
Help me ask your landlady about her.
Am I the kind of person who gossips?
Oh, right,
you are a tall, rich, and handsome guy
dating a supermodel.
Of course, you don't understand
the misery of us single people.
Oh, you broke up with her.
I forgot. Sorry.
It's only because you don't
really look heartbroken.
You even seem
to have gained some weight.
Impossible!
Really.
I do seem to have gained some weight.
I shouldn't eat too much
of my landlady's cooking.
Your landlady cooks for you?
Well, well, Li Yifei,
no wonder you're glowing
even after a breakup.
You're already dating a new one
so quickly?
As expected of you.
Don't slander me.
Just look at her.
Is she even my type?
If she's not your type,
why are you still staying here?
Didn't you say Gui Lili rented this place,
and you were not satisfied?
I still need money to move out.
If you want to move out,
there are millions of ways to do it.
There's only one reason
for you to stay.
I will just ignore you.
[Shanghai World Financial Center]
[Marketing Department]
[Marketing Director's Office]
[He Jing Securities Co., Ltd.]
Don't worry.
I've already put your research report
in your role model's office.
Just wait for the reply.
[Thank you, Yu.]
[Marketing Director's Office]
I'm back.
How could you even eat such a thing?
What are you doing?
I'm telling you.
In this house,
no one is allowed to eat junk food.
You're not the landlord.
Why should I follow your rules?
Since we're sharing a house,
we should be considerate.
You're eating something
with such a strong smell.
It makes me
feel nauseous.
I'll just eat in my room, okay?
So anything is fine in the room, huh?
Then can I smoke in my room, too?
How is that the same?
If you smoke a cigarette,
the smell will linger all day.
I can still smell it.
It's the same logic.
I won't smoke in my room,
and you don't eat instant noodles
in yours.
This is my dinner, bro.
I'll order takeout for dinner.
Takeout isn't
any healthier than instant noodles.
Don't worry.
The takeout I order is
definitely delicious, healthy,
and nutritionally balanced.
How much did this meal cost?
Forget about it.
I didn't ask you to pay.
I'm not trying to take advantage of you.
You threw my dinner away,
so I had to...
Alright, alright.
Cut the crap and eat up.
I'll dig in then.
Thanks for the meal.
What have you been busy with today
that you didn't even bother to cook?
Although I submitted the research report,
it only scratches the surface.
Shanlifang is very complicated.
I need to investigate further.
You're so proactive?
Did Fang Yun agree to reinstate you?
Not yet,
but it's always right
to be prepared in advance.
But it's been a while.
Why are there still no updates yet?
I only submitted
the research report yesterday.
It's only been a day. No rush.
Based on what you know about Fang Yun,
do you think she'd put off today's work
until tomorrow?
Something must have gone wrong.
Yu is the receptionist.
It was already against the rules for her
to put it on the office desk.
I can't ask her to do more,
as it will just affect her work.
Then you should go
and hand it to her in person.
Don't tell me you don't even have
the guts to do that.
It's not that I don't have the guts.
I just think
my work results are
enough to speak for themselves,
and I don't need to do anything else.
If it were really only about work results,
you wouldn't have been
laid off, got it?
You sound like you know me pretty well.
After reading your research report,
I do have some understanding of you.
So you mean
you recognize my work capability?
Yup.
Seeing you so pitiful and unemployed,
I can't help but be kind
and comfort you a bit.
I don't need any comfort.
I, Qian Fei,
will definitely prove myself
to all of you.
These shrimp are good, too. Try some.
Didn't you say
it was unhealthy junk food?
Delicious junk food.
But it's still not as good
as the stir-fried eggplant you cook.
[Shanghai World Financial Center]
Director Fang,
this is my research report on Shanlifang.
I've had
a copy put on your office desk earlier.
You might have already seen it.
I want to know where its flaws are.
You know I'm very busy,
with no spare time to waste
on reading an amateur piece
written by a layman.
But, Director Fang,
all the statistics, explanations,
and content I did
will definitely be helpful to the progress
of your project team.
I'm very confident about that.
Satisfied?
If someone is
very capable at work
but not recognized by the company,
they won't have the chance
to show their abilities.
So someone who doesn't know
how to appreciate
what they have will never be of any value,
understand?
[He Jing Securities Co., Ltd.]
Director Fang,
I was afraid Qian Fei would bother you,
so I took that...
[He Jing Securities Co., Ltd.]
Do you think
my office is where anyone can enter
and take whatever they want?
No, no, Director Fang.
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
I was wrong. I won't do it ever again.
You may leave now.
[He Jing Securities Co., Ltd.]
I'm hungry! Hurry up and cook!
You're bossing me around
as soon as I'm back!
Do you have any humanity?
You still owe me a meal, remember?
You promised it.
You should have still
made an appointment with me in advance!
There are no ingredients left at home now,
so I can't cook.
Who says you can't?
I've bought the groceries.
They're in the kitchen.
You actually bought groceries?
I ordered them on my phone,
and they were delivered home directly.
As a modern person,
don't you even know this?
Hurry up and cook.
He actually bought them.
Never thought I'd see this.
Young master, come out for dinner.
He can't hear me?
Are you done eavesdropping?
I just wanted to see
if this door was soundproof.
It's soundproof when I want it to be
and not soundproof when I don't.
Is it any of your business?
Not bad.
You met Fang Yun?
It's hopeless?
Landlady.
Did you
ever expect
that we'd end up like this one day?
Like what?
Sitting here and having a heart-to-heart?
Never.
I never thought
there'd be a day like this in my life.
Because in my eyes, you used to be
a pervert.
And to me, you were a shrew.
You know what?
You should thank God—
you're so lucky
to have such a handsome tenant.
Handsome? Let me check.
Do you even need to check?
Two eyes,
one nose,
and one mouth.
Yeah, pretty handsome.
But what's the use of being handsome?
Look at the way you act.
I really can't approve of it.
Look at you,
living like this,
sharing a house with others,
and also wasting money.
I can't stand it.
I really can't stand to see it.
If you can't stand it, just don't look.
So,
hurry up and find a chance
to move out soon.
We're a single man and a single woman.
It's really inappropriate
for us to live together.
Hey,
isn't your dad living here in Shanghai?
Why don't you move back home?
Why do you insist on living
away from home?
My dad and I don't get along.
He's never approved
of anything I did since I was a child.
He is definitely the happiest person
to see me sad or having a hard time.
How could that be?
You are father and son. You're family.
What family?
Let me tell you a story. Back then,
when my mom was seriously ill
and only had a few days left,
during her most difficult
and painful time,
we didn't even know where he was.
He just left the two of us.
We didn't know
if he was messing around somewhere
or hustling somewhere.
Is that a family?
What?
Why are you crying? I'm fine now.
-It's not for you. It's about myself.
-I haven't cried, but why are you crying?
I'm crying not because of you,
but because of myself.
What's wrong with you?
Your talk about your mother
reminded me of my mother as well.
My mother used to tell me
to study hard
and get into a good university.
And the result?
I ended up like this.
If my mother were alive
and saw me like this,
she would definitely be very sad.
I spent my best years
on dating
and thought getting married
and having a house
would be the peak of my life.
But God was just punishing me.
I got dumped and fired,
and now I'm in massive debt.
If my mom learned about this,
how heartbroken she would be.
Landlady,
this is life,
and it's no big deal.
We all encounter all kinds of things.
Landlady? Qian Fei?
I can't believe it.
How come you instantly
pass out every time you drink?
Seriously?
Alright, don't sleep here.
You'll catch a cold.
Come on, go back. Go back to sleep.
Oh, my God.
Are you completely unconscious?
Come on.
Get up now. Go back to sleep.
Don't sleep here.
I give up. Fine, fine.
I'll settle the score with you tomorrow.
Come on.
How could you drink yourself
straight into a coma?
No matter what, Fang Yun's side
should be making a big move.
Why is there no reaction at all?
Seems like this trick didn't work.
I must confront her directly.
I'm in a hurry.
Let me use the mirror first.
Can you wait your turn?
You don't go to work.
Y-You're not in a hurry.
Excuse me?
-Let me check. I'm in a rush.
-First come, first served.
You don't go to work.
Why did you have to fight me for it?
I'm leaving. Bye-bye.
So what if you have a job?
Director Fang wants to meet me?
This is a research report
written by a former
back-office employee.
I didn't bring this out
for any other reason
but to make you feel ashamed.
These are the most valuable words
I have ever seen in the past 2 weeks.
If you, investment banking elites
who work with me,
have any sense of shame,
you should carefully review
the work you're doing.
Got it?
Xinyao.
Make 10 copies of this.
Director Fang,
then should we
follow the ideas of this research report
and continue...
Continue what?
Continue to get yourselves fired like her?
You just jump to conclusions.
I'm asking you to sum it up.
Don't be so dejected
just because I criticized you a bit.
The people from Zhizhong Investment
will arrive soon.
Hurry up and pull yourselves together.
Since you don't have an appointment,
please leave your name
and contact information.
I will have him contact you
when he gets back.
[He Jing Securities Co., Ltd.]
[Meeting Room]
See?
Here,
[The Market Share
of Shanlifang Hotel Group]
I combined the contents
of this research report
with the ones you guys wrote.
Director Fang used the integrated analysis
from my research report.
It seems that she really called me over
to recruit me into the team.
You're here.
Yes, I'm back.
[Meeting Room]
Alright.
Then, Mr. Li, let's get started.
Okay.
[In the next episode
of "Love Has Fireworks"]
[Empower the Future with Gratitude
for Everyone—2018 Annual Gala Report]
[Certificate for Employee of the Year
in Shanlifang Hotel Group]
The annual gala...
The annual gala from 3 years ago...
Have you made up your mind?
I'm going on vacation.
Okay.
Then have a good time.
Goodbye.
What's your name?
Xin Ba.
Xin Ba,
I'm the big boy, Li Yifei.
Nice to meet you.
Alright, big boy.